<resources>
    <string name="app_name">InfoParks</string>
    <string name="samburu">Enjoy a quintessential Kenyan northern safari with unrestricted access to rugged East African wilderness by including Samburu National Reserve in your bush plans! The 165-square kilometers (64 square miles) reserve is located northeast of Laikipia and is home to some of Africa’s rarest flora and fauna.</string>
    <string name="laikipia">Laikipia National Reserve is a remote and truly wild corner of Kenya, the Laikipia National Park boasts incredible game viewing in a spectacularly beautiful setting. Two rivers, the Ewaso Nyiro and Ewaso Narok run through the area, attracting a rich variety of wildlife, including the second largest population of elephant in Kenya.</string>
    <string name="shaba">Shaba National Reserve in northern Kenya offers the astute African traveler 92 square miles (239 square kilometers) of breathtaking scenery amidst arid grasslands and sparse woodland set against the backdrop hills of Shaba, a volcanic extinct highland. The reserve is named for the 1525-meter Mount Shaba that was the yesteryear source of varied lava flow across the reserve. Along the northern border, the Ewaso Nyiro River winds through deep gorges, along sandbanks, then cascades down Chandler’s Falls and finally draining it all at Lorian Swamp. </string>
    <string name="mtKenya">Climbing to 5,199 meters, Mount Kenya is the second tallest mountain in Africa. The scenery surrounding this designated World Heritage Site is breath-taking. It is pristine wilderness with lakes, tarns, glaciers, dense forest, mineral springs and a selection of rare and endangered species of animals, high altitude adapted plains game and unique montane and alpine vegetation. Visitors can enjoy mountain climbing, camping and caving with the mountains rugged glacier-clad peaks providing the perfect backdrop.</string>
    <string name="aberdare">Picturesque, steep forested ravines and open moorland characterise the Aberdare National Park. The park provides a habitat for elephants, black rhinos, leopards, spotted hyenas, olive baboons, black and white colobus monkeys, buffalos, warthogs and bushbucks among others. Rare sightings include those of the Giant Forest hog, bongo, golden cat, serval cat, African wild cat, African civet cat and the blue duiker. Visitors can indulge in picnics, trout fishing in the rivers and camping in the moorlands. Bird viewing is rewarding, with over 250 species of birds in the park, including the Francolin, Sparrow hawks, goshawks, eagles, sunbirds and plovers.</string>
    <string name="tsavoEast">Tsavo East National Park</string>
    <string name="tsavodes">Tsavo East National Park is one of the oldest and largest parks in Kenya at 13,747 square kilometres. Situated in a semi-arid area previously known as the Taru Desert it opened in April 1948, it is located near the town of Voi in the Taita-Taveta County of the former Coast Province. </string>
</resources>
